# **Caleb Parris**

Web Developer

(432) 934- 2795

Calebparris@live.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/calebparris

https://calebparris.github.io/react-portfolio/

https://github.com/CalebParris

### SUMMARY

I am seeking a career in Web Development. My background includes five years of network focused work and technical support. My current and former roles are deeply reliant on strong communication, attention to fine details, and time management skills which I successfully demonstrate. I graduated from a vocational school (Vantage College) and earned the following CompTIA certifications: Network+, Security+, and A+. I have two to three years of formal university coursework completed and have learned multiple computer languages at the University of Austin coding Bootcamp. These experiences have sharpened my skill set vastly.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Interactions LLC

Remote — T1 Support Specialist October 2017- November 2020

- Adjusts and tests Customer IVR test scripts
- Opens, updates, and Closes Tickets

**GTT** 

Austin, Texas — NOC Engineer August 2015 - October 2017

- Business to business technical support
- Promoted to Tier II team

Time Warner Cable

Austin, Texas— Overnight Technical Support March 2015 - August 2015

Troubleshooting of consumer internet services

## **EDUCATION**

University of Texas Austin Coding Bootcamp

July 2020 - December 2020

Full Stack Completion Certification

Western Governor's University

August 2018- May 2020

Studied Network Operations and Security

# Vantage College

March 2014 - October 2015

- Earned multiple CompTIA Certifications
- Graduated from Network Administrator and Computer Systems Program

### PROJECT SAMPLE

Local Hops - Find and save your favorite local breweries to a personalized account.

This project was created using JavaScript, Handlebars, and CSS

https://local-texas-hops.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/CalebParris/Local-Hops